Sosu, my target has appeared.
Konvosusu. Dimara Sosu.
Hey, wait!
Huh?
Forearms, high body temperature.
The scent of the sun.
A hollow?
But she's... she's so well put together.
Same as Nanachi.
Sosu, what has happened to your arm?
Did somebody hurt you?
Reg!
Reg.
Have I... have I met her before?
Who did this, Sosu?
What? Who are you?
Are you the one who left us that creepy note before?
Hmm...
Oh!
Hadima...
Oogu?
What is it?
Hey!
Furu-de-fur-bearer?
Do not like lots of eyes looking, Sosu.
What?
Fakta.
Born out of longing.
A longing too fragile, too deep.
You left her to posterity.
You had to...
you had to...
We had...
Fear.
Letam out of your soul...
The comm device isn't getting through. Must be blocked or something.
Aw, jeez. I hope he's not being reckless.
Hagi. Nice smelling fluffy one.
Snannichi.
Nice smelling nannichi. You have yet to change your value into iru, currency.
There is water and fruit for your sustenance, but here value is needed to train.
I see. What should I do?
Would stomping on that flat guy get me some extra value?
Hey, Maji Kaja. About that balancing thing.
Was it what Riko said that decided the amount of Mania's value?
Inga, no.
It wasn't?
Kaja said before, but iru buru, the village knows everyone's desires.
And how, you might ask? By looking at signals.
At signals? You mean in your head?
The head alone is not sufficient. They are deeper. Signals of the soul that include one's connections.
No matter what the mouth says, signals of the soul cannot be fooled.
But aren't there people who really believe the lies that they tell themselves?
If the soul is unsteady, one can fool themselves with their own words. Their truth is their own.
Before long, it becomes a signal of the soul.
Minyu, what is of value to Nanachi?
To me?
Let me think.
Mitty and...
Padi.
Mitty.
Yeah, Mitty.
And the people I'm with.
Don't care about the rest.
Kaja understands.
Mitty smells very nice.
Kaja wants her as well.
Though Beloff of the three sages is using her.
Oh, Mitty.
That warm mass of the torturous curse the masked man left cruelly behind.
Hey, what do you mean?
Maya, the three sages are the ones who created this place.
Not that part.
Huh?
Was I mistaken in what you said?
The masked man left who behind exactly?
Huh?
Where am I?
Why are you being like this?
Did you also forget this place, Sosu?
I feel bad about replying to a question with a question.
But what kind of relationship is there between you and me?
I feel as though I've met you before.
But, well, it would seem I might have lost my memories of that time.
I want to know what I am and all the memories I lost.
So, if you know, then please tell me.
Fopta must check to see if you're you.
If you're really reg.
Then Fopta will answer.
That's all right with me?
I just gotta hope she doesn't notice the comm device.
Show Fopta that too, Sosu.
Oh.
Hey.
Aren't you going to ask me anything?
Even though you're Fopta's, who'd do this?
What is this wound, Sosu?
No, no, don't touch it.
It's not fully healed just yet.
I, I can't move.
Taste is the same.
You said you would bring Haku back here, Sosu.
Human child or hollow child?
Which one is it you call your Haku, Sosu?
What'd you say?
Haku?
Haku.
One's highest valued thing.
One's most dear.
Yes, you are Fopta's reg.
Show me just in case.
You leave me alone.
I came here to find out who I am, not get violated.
And first of all, you shouldn't know me as Reg.
That's the name Riko gave me on the surface.
That can't be right, Sosu.
Reg was also Reg before Riko.
It would appear speaking with you is proving to be pointless.
Fopta is not lying!
Reg, where are you going, Sosu?
Sorry, but I'll be heading back now.
Riko and Nanachi are waiting for me.
Reg, so you want to live in the same time as the human child?
Even when they die, you will stay the same.
What will you do, Sosu?
I'll stay with them until the very end, as a friend should.
And when the time comes, I'll have to deal with it, then.
Egu, Egu, Konbu, Sosu.
That clock tower.
I saw it when we first came down here.
Don't attack me, okay?
I'm leaving.
Damn it.
My stupid body.
My bigger injuries heal up right away.
So Fopta, the embodiment of value, will never perish.
She certainly was very beautiful.
But what did I do to her in the past for her to act that way?
So you...
You want to live in the same time as the human child?
Makes me wonder.
Back then, how would I have answered that question?
Even if I get my memories back,
will I...
Will I be able to stay the way I am?
What is all this?
They're...
They're eternal fortunes.
Petals of the flowers of fortitude.
And all these...
All these nameplates.
Eternal fortunes are scattered for celebrations and...
And funerals.
Are all these people...
Deceased?
I don't understand.
What is happening to the Abyss?
I don't think I can get used to this toilet.
It's nice it keeps wiping your butt for you, but...
The toilet with tentacles eats bugs!
Reg?
Nanachi?
Drink lots of water if you get diarrhea.
It can sometimes be fatal.
Reg?
Hey Nanachi!
I have a bad feeling about this.
Um...
Do you know where my two friends went?
One has ears like this?
Nana.
Uh...
Outside?
Where could those two have gone?
Uh...
Oh no !
Reg!
Nanachi!
Oooooo?
Nanachi?!
Huh?
Ha...
Oh...
I hid without even thinking.
When they come back, give them this.
Understand?
Oh, and this is for the room.
Fubu?
Um, okay.
Sure.
Yeah, that sounds good.
I hope I can get there without getting lost.
I hardly know anything at all about this village.
Puma.
Yeah, I know.
Of course, I need to be very careful.
But let's hurry.
Uh, do you know who Maji Kaja is?
Odema.
Maji Kaja.
Mademo.
You don't understand, huh?
Thanks anyway.
See ya.
I'll look for them at the market.
They're following us.
They're not the same ones from yesterday, right?
Um, I know where the market is, so...
Ga-mu Maji Kaja.
Kaja?
Sengay.
captcha.
Ma-mu Mansa.
Sengay.
So.
Okay.
This way?
Huh?
It's gotta be physical.
Stop.
Okay.
Happy cuarto.
Let's be patient.
mitä?
It needs pain to help him in those ways.
Um, hey, uh, if you damage my value at all, you know, you'll face that horrible balancing
thing.
You better run.
Hey, stop!
This is bad.
No!
You're not alone!
No, no, don't!
Ma!
It's that piercing sound.
The same one from the balancing.
Ma!
I guess my helmet got eaten back there.
The black things aren't coming after us.
Well, that's good.
Looks like the balancing didn't come here for this one.
Ma!
Even with this, neither Reg nor Nanachi have come out. Something must have happened to him.
I'm sorry, but I have to leave you behind to go find my friends. Thanks for saving us today. I'll return the favor sometime.
Ma! Say, how about we go together? Ma! Ma!
So, uh, what's your name? Ma! Let's see. Can I just call you Ma? Ma! Can you show me where to go so I don't get lost? Ma!
Did you hear that noise just now? The sound of the balancing.
Yes, but it appears to have just ended. Does it worry you?
No. Just hurry up and lead the way.
It's super crowded today, isn't it? But that's okay. I'm used to crowds from my time working as a tour guide back home.
Ma! Ma!
I wonder where those two could have gone.
Oh, something smells really delicious.
Uh...
Oh! Is that... I think it is!
Oh! A restaurant!
Oh, wow! Never eaten out before except at Auntie's place.
Drink some water if you get diarrhea.
And even if you're not feeling hungry, be sure to eat.
This place is packed. And there's a hint of poo mixed in with all the good smells.
I can feel the pulse of the hollow next to me racing.
Is that a menu? Can't understand it anyway.
I wonder what I can say.
I want to order one of the dishes that smells yummy.
Check up a poo!
Ma!
Uh...
Let's see.
That one?
Kanbosu.
Ma-ma!
That little guy's mouth looks like mine.
So, I should be able to eat that too.
Here's your smile.
Huh? Is this the right thing?
Paddy?
Oh! This must be kind of like a spoon.
Ah!
This is the smell that brought me here!
Whoa!
Look at all this stuff.
Did they smoke it all together?
Isn't the spoon a bit small for so much food?
Hot!
It's so spicy, my ears hurt!
I could eat this whole day!
I take it you like it.
I want Nanaji to try this too.
Huh?
Wait!
Hey, I just understood you!
That's roasted testicle, you know.
Nobody serves it around here but me.
There's someone of Arankaja who speaks the same language as me.
Well, sure.
And some others too.
The one over there, for example.
Uh...
That's Wazukyan, of the Three Sages.
Belaf, Katja is coming in.
Uh...
That's Wazukyan, of the Three Sages.
Belaf, Katja is coming in.
Come in.
There is, When Arankajk.
You never heard of the three sea Chat쪽에,
Sean!
You have come in.
Do you take bets here?
Uh...
川ekajk is coming in.
Oh...
33!
Oh, my God.
Amiri.
Once one has finally found their treasure, one's value will transition, and one's journey will end.
Thank you.